// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " 10 / 2 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " 22 / 1 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "22",
    options: [
      "22",
      "11",
      "1",
      "21"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 15 / 3 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "4",
      "6",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " 60 / 4 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "22",
      "20",
      "15",
      "6"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Is 95 is divisible by 5",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "None of the above",
      "Don't Know"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Is 100 is divisible by 2",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "None of the above",
      "Don't Know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Is 25 is divisible by 2",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "None of the above",
      "Don't Know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A boy had total 50 pens. He gave equal pens among 10 friends, How many pens each friend get?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "There are total 20 soaps and packets comes with 4 soaps per packet. How many such packets will be there?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
        "5",
        "6",
        "4",
        "3"
      ]
  },
  /*
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 9 * 9 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "81",
    options: [
      "18",
      "88",
      "17",
      "81"
    ]
  }
  */
];
